{
    "subject": "Yang_Jiang",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Qian_Zhongshu",
    "human_readable": "Yang Jiang is married to Qian Zhongshu.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.964443027973175,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage between Yang Jiang and Qian Zhongshu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9366161823272705,
            "question": "To whom is Qian Zhongshu married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9276889562606812,
            "question": "Is Qian Zhongshu married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9227880239486694,
            "question": "Who is Yang Jiang married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8932906985282898,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Yang Jiang and Qian Zhongshu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8889118432998657,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Yang Jiang."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8363726735115051,
            "question": "Who is Yang Jiang's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7884781360626221,
            "question": "Is there a known connection between Yang Jiang and Qian Zhongshu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.757523775100708,
            "question": "What is the name of Yang Jiang's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6945597529411316,
            "question": "Are Yang Jiang and Qian Zhongshu known to each other?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Yang Jiang is married to Qian Zhongshu.",
            "html": "yago_25199_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Yang Jiang's husband?",
            "html": "yago_25199_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a known connection between Yang Jiang and Qian Zhongshu?",
            "html": "yago_25199_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Yang Jiang's husband?",
            "html": "yago_25199_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25199_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25199_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25199_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25199_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25199_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25199_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25199_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25199_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25199_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25199_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple, as there are multiple mentions of Yang Jiang's marriage to Qian Zhongshu. For example, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25199/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt states that \"Yang Jiang, wife of Qian Zhongshu\", and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25199/re-ranker-msmarco/66.txt mentions Yang Jiang as the wife of Qian Zhongshu in a photo caption."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Yang Jiang was married to Qian Zhongshu, supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}